I can't believe you'd actually say that.
我真不敢相信你會這麼說
I'd much rather be Mr. Peanut than Mr. Salty.
我是鹽先生而非花生先生?
No way. Mr. Salty is a sailor.
才怪,鹽先生是個水手
He's gotta be the toughest snack there is.
他應該是最頑強的點心
I don't know. You don't wanna mess with Cornnuts.
我不知道,你不會想和玉米作對的
They're crazy.
它們簡直是瘋了
Oh,my God. You gotta come see this.
上帝呀.你應該看看這個
There's some creep out there with a telescope.
有個變態拿著望遠鏡
I can't believe it. He's looking right at us.
我真不敢相信他在看我們
Oh,that is so sick.
真嘔心
I feel violated.
我感覺被冒犯了
And not in a good way.
而且很不爽
How can people do that?
怎會有人這樣?
You guys,look. Ugly Naked Guy got gravity boots.
你們看,醜陋裸男有雙重力鞋
The One With the Evil Orthodontist
六人行 第1季 第20集 風流牙醫
-=BT之家DRM小組 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 榮譽出品 河馬根據網絡字幕微調製作
Years from now, school children will study it...
幾年後學童將會把它奉為…
...as one of the greatest first dates ever.
第一次約會的經典加以研讀
-Yeah. -I'll say,yeah.
-是的 -要我說,當然
It was unbelievable.
它太令人無法置信
We could be ourselves. We didn't have to play games.
我們可以完全作自己,無須再玩任何遊戲
-Have you called her? -She'd know I like her. That's crazy.
-你打過電話給她沒? -讓她知道我喜歡她?你瘋了不成
Guys. It's gross.
夥計.你可真毛糙啊
It's the next day. How needy do I wanna seem?
才第二天,你要我顯得多渴望?
-I'm right. Right? -Yeah,let her dangle.
-對吧 -對,讓她慢慢等吧
I can't believe my parents are pushing me to find one of you people.
我無法相信我爸媽,強迫我找你們這種男人
Come on. Just do it.
快,只管去做
Call her. Stop being so testosterone-y.
拿起電話打給她 別擺出一付臭男人的樣子(義同睪丸素)
Which,by the way, is the real San Francisco treat.
對了,舊金山真有這道菜
-Her machine. -Answering machine?
-是機器 -她的答錄機?
No,interestingly, her leaf blower picked up.
不,真有意思,是落葉清掃機
So,why didn't you say anything?
你為何不說話?
No. Last time I left a spontaneous message...
不行,上次我留話時
... I ended up using the phrase, "Yes,indeed-io."
結果說了「對,的確」
Look,it's Rachel and Barry. Don't everybody look.
看,是瑞秋和巴瑞,不,別一起看
What's going on?
怎麼了?
-They're just talking. -Does he look upset?
-他們只是在講話 -他是否神情落寞?
Does he look like he was told to shove anything?
他是否像被告知去死的樣子?
No. Actually,he's smiling.
沒有,而且他正在微笑
Oh,my God. Don't do that.
我的老天,不要那樣干?
What? What? What?
怎麼啦?怎麼啦?怎麼啦?
That man across the street just kicked that pigeon.
對街的男人踢了一隻鴿子
And basically,that's how a bill becomes a law.
這就是法案成為法律的原因
See? Hey,Rach.
看?嗨,瑞秋
How'd it go?
情況如何?
You know,it was actually really great.
你們知道嗎,真的,真的好極了
Lunch at the Russian Tea Room.
他帶我到俄國茶室吃飯
I had that chicken,where you poke it and butter squirts out.
我點了那種雞肉 一刺就有奶油嘖出來的那種
Not a good day for birds.
今天真不是鳥兒的好日子
Then we went to Bendel's.
然後我們去精品店
And I told him not to,but he got me a bottle of Chanel.
我告訴他不要,他還是買了香奈兒給我
That's nice. Now was that before or after you told him...
真體貼.是在你跟他說之前還是之後送的
...to stop calling,stop sending flowers and to leave you alone?
叫他別再打電話來, 別再送你花,別再來煩你?
Right. Well,we never actually got to that.
老實說我沒機會開口
It was just so nice to see him again.
能再見到他的感覺真好
It was comfortable and it was familiar.
感覺是那麼自在而熟悉
It was just nice.
感覺真好
That's nice twice.
你已講了兩遍
Isn't this the same Barry who you left at the altar?
他不是在聖壇前被你甩掉的巴瑞嗎?
Where have you been?
你上哪兒去了?
It was different with him today.
今天和他在一起感覺不同
He wasn't,like,Orthodontist Guy.
他今天不像是牙醫
I mean,we had fun. Is there anything wrong with that?
我們玩得很開心,這樣有什麼不對嗎?
-Why? -I have my reasons.
-為什麼? -我有我的理由
He's engaged to another woman...
他訂婚的對象…
...who happens to be your ex-best friend?
是你前任的知己呢?
All right. I know it's stupid.
好吧!我知道這樣做很傻
I'll see him this afternoon and put an end to it.
我下午去找他談分手
I'm not crazy,right? I mean,it was never like that.
我不瘋狂吧?我從未像這樣
No,it wasn't.
從未
It was so nice having this little sink here.
這兒有個小水槽真好
Then with authority,hang up.
還掛著…證書
Will you just leave her the message?
你到底留言不?
Okay. All right,fine.
好的,這就說
"Oh,Danielle, I wasn't expecting the machine.
丹妮爾,沒想到是答錄機接的
Give me a call when you get a chance.
有空請回電
Bye-bye.
再見
Oh,God.
哦,天哪
That's what you've been working on for two hours?
你這兩小時都在忙這個?
Hey,I've been honing.
我在演練
-What was with the dishes? -She might think I'm in a restaurant.
-和盤子有何關係? -我要她以為我在餐廳
I might have a life. Like I haven't been sitting here...
我過著不錯的生活
... honing for the last two hours?
不是只在這兒演練數小時的樣子
-The telescope guy's doing it again. -Oh,my God.
-看,又是那個拿望遠鏡的人. -哦,我的上帝
Go away. Stop looking in here.
拜託,走開,別再往這兒看
Great. Now he's waving back.
這下可好,他也揮手了
We gotta do something.
我們得想辦法阻止他
I caught him looking into our place. I feel like I can't do stuff.
早上我逮到他往這兒看 真是令我毛骨驚然,我感覺自己無法辦事
What kind of stuff?
什麼樣的事情呀?
Will you grow up? I'm not talking about sexy stuff...
成熟點行嗎,我不是指性
...but,like, when I'm cooking naked.
我只是光著屁股做飯
You cook naked?
你光著屁股做飯?
Yeah,toast,oatmeal. Nothing that spatters.
對,吐司,燕麥,不會濺出來的東西
What are you looking at me for? I didn't know that.
看我幹嘛?我毫不知情
What's the matter?
怎麼了?
I just Oh,Barry,this was not good.
巴瑞,這樣不好
No,it was. It was very,very good.
不,不好.是非常非常不好
-What about Mindy? -Way better than Mindy.
-明蒂呢? -我們幹得比明蒂好多了
I mean,what about you and Mindy?
不,我是指你和明蒂
If you want,I'll break it off with her.
如果你願意我就和她分手
No,don't do that. Not for me.
萬萬不行,別那樣做.別為我那樣做
Dr. Farber,Bobby Rush is here for his adjustment.
法大夫,巴比來做調整
Thanks,Bernice.
謝謝
Let's go away this weekend.
我們週末去渡假
-This is all way too -No,we can go to Aruba.
-巴瑞,這樣太… -不,或許我們可以去阿魯已
When I went there on what would've been our honeymoon...
我在「蜜月」時去過了
...it was really nice. You would've liked it.
感覺很棒,你一定會喜歡的
I had a bra.
我本來有穿胸罩
Hey,Dr. Farber.
法大夫
All right,Miss Greene, everything looks fine.
格林小姐,看來一切正常
We're starting to see some real progress.
進步許多
-What? -I'm 1 2,I'm not stupid.
-幹嘛? -我十二歲了,我不笨
Can I use your phone?
能借用你的電話嗎?
For future reference, that thing in your hand...
我指點你一下,你拿的那支…
...can also be used as a phone.
…也可以當電話使
Yes,it's working.
這電話沒問題啊
-Why isn't she calling? -Maybe she never got your message.
-她為何不回電? -或許她沒聽到你的留言
Call her machine, and if she has a lot of beeps...
如果願意你可以打給她的留言機 如果她聽見許多嗶聲
...that means she didn't get her messages yet.
那代表她或許沒聽見留言
-Doesn't that make me seem? -Desperate? Needy? Pathetic?
-難道你不認為這樣會使我感覺有點 -絕望,渴望,可悲?
You obviously saw my personal ad.
你顯然看過我的霉友啟事
How many beeps?
嗶幾聲?
She answered.
她接的
This is where you'd use that "hello" word.
此時你該向她打招呼才對
I won't talk to her. She got my message...
我不能跟她講話,她顯然聽到我的留言
...and is choosing not to call me. Now I'm needy and snubbed.
而且選擇不回電,我既渴望又被人冷落
God,I miss just being needy.
我真想念純渴望的滋味
So how'd he take it?
嘿,他表現如何?
Pretty well,actually.
事實上,還不錯
How come you have dental floss in your hair?
你頭髮上為何有牙線?
Oh,do l?
有嗎?
-We ended up having sex in his chair. -You had sex in his chair?
-我們在他椅上做愛 -你們在他椅上做愛?
I said that a little too loudly,didn't l?
我是否說得太大聲?
You had what?
你們什麼?
Sex in his chair.
在他椅上做愛
What...? What were you thinking?
你到底在想什麼?
I don't know. We still care about each other.
我也不知道,我們仍在乎對方
There's a history there. It's like you and Carol.
我們曾相愛過,就像你和卡蘿一樣
It's nothing like me and Carol.
不,不像我和卡蘿
If she said to you, "Ross,I want you on this couch...
如果她說:羅斯我要你躺在這沙發上
... right here,right now," what would you say?
此時此地,你會怎麼回答?
If it helps,I could slide over.
如果需要我可以過去點
It's a totally different situation. It's apples and oranges.
這完全是兩回事,這是蘋果和桔子
It's orthodontists and lesbians I gotta go.
牙醫和女同志,我走了
-Where are you going? -I just have to go.
-你要上哪兒去? -我就是要走,行嗎?
I have things to do with my life.
我有自己的人生要過
I have a jam-packed schedule.
我有許多事要做
And I am late for keeping up with it,okay?
被某事耽擱了
Mindy.
明蒂
How are you?
你好
Yes,I heard. Congratulations. That is so great.
對,我聽說了,恭喜.這真是太好了
Really,oh,God
真的,哦,上帝啊
I'm working tomorrow,but if you want,you can come by if you'd like.
我明天要上班,如果願意可以到店裡
Great.
太好了
So I'll see you tomorrow.
明天見了
Okay. Bye.
ok,再見
Oh,God. Oh,God.
天呀 天呀 天呀
So how's Mindy?
明蒂好嗎?
She wants to see me tomorrow. She sounded weird. I gotta call Barry.
她明天想見我, 她的語調好詭異,我得打電話給巴瑞
It's me. I just Mindy.
是我,我只是,明蒂
Mindy. No,I figured that's where you'd be.
明蒂.我想你可能會在那兒
Hell is filled with people like you.
你這種人都該下地獄
He's back. The peeper's back.
偷窺狂又出現了,蹲下
-Get down. -Get down?
-蹲下? -蹲下?
And boogie.
接著跳舞
I gotta go and get my eyes scratched out by Mindy.
我得去上班,接受明蒂的審判
She may not even know.
放輕鬆,或許她還不知道
I haven't heard from her in seven months,what else is it about?
拜託,我們七個月來沒連絡過 她突然打電話來還會有什麼事呢?
She was my best friend.
她曾是我最要好的朋友
We went to camp together, she taught me how to kiss....
我們一起去夏令營,她教我如何親吻
Now,you know, I'm,like,the other woman.
是嗎?如今我像是成了第三者
-I feel so -Naughty.
-我感覺自己很…-頑皮
-See you later. -I'll walk with you.
-回頭見了.-我和你一起出去
When she taught you to kiss,were you wearing any kind of little uniform?
她在夏令營時教你親吻,你穿著制服,或著…
That's fine,yeah.
沒事了.
I'm going to the bathroom. Will you watch my phone?
我要上洗手間,幫我守著電話好嗎?
-Take it with you. -We haven't had a second date...
-你何不帶進去? -我們還沒第二次約會
-...she needs to hear me pee? -Why don't you call her?
-她需要聽到我尿尿的聲音嗎? -何不乾脆打給她?
I can't. I left a message. I have some pride.
我已留言,不能打給她.我有男性的尊嚴
-Do you? -No.
-有嗎? -沒有
Danielle,hi.
丹妮爾
It's Chandler.
是我,錢德
I'm fine.
我很好
Listen....
聽著…
I don't know if you tried to call me because...
我不知道你是否打過電話給我
... I accidentally shut off my phone.
因為我是個白癡不小心把電話關了
That's fine. That's great. Okay.
好,太好了
She's on the other line. She's gonna call me back.
她正在講電話,等一下會回我電話
She's on the other line, she's gonna call me back.
她正在講電話,等一下會回我電話…
-Don't you have to pee? -That's why I'm dancing.
-你不想尿了? -這就是我跳舞的原因
-Mindy. -Hey,you.
-明蒂. -嗨,你好
Hey,you.
嗨,你好
So what's up?
什麼事?
We should really be sitting for this.
我們該坐下來談
Sure we should.
當然啦
I'm gonna ask once, and I want a straight answer.
我只問一次,我希望你直接回答
Not like when I asked if those red pants made my ass look big.
這好像在問,紅色短褲是不是 讓我的屁股顯得大一些一樣
I know things have been weird...
我感覺最近有點奇怪
...but you're my oldest friend, except for Laurie...
你是我認識最久的朋友,除了蘿瑞之外
...who's bitter because she lost weight...
她雖已減肥成功
...and it turns out, she doesn't have a pretty face.
但是,臉蛋依然醜陋
-Okay,I'm just gonna say it. -Okay.
-我要說了啊. -好的
Will you be my maid of honor?
願意當我的伴娘嗎?
-Of course. -That's so great.
-當然! -太好了
It is. It is. It is.
這是,這是,這是
-That's all you wanted to ask? -That's all.
-這就是你想問我的事? -對,就這樣
-What? -That's not all.
-怎麼了? -不,不只這樣
-Oh,sure it is. -Oh,no,it isn't.
-當然是的 -也不全是
I think Barry's seeing someone in the city.
我認為巴瑞有其他的女人
What would make you think that?
你怎會這樣想?
Since the engagement, he's acted weird.
宣佈訂婚後他就變了樣
And then last night,he came home smelling like Chanel.
昨晚他回家時有香奈兒的味道
Really?
真的?
If it'll make you feel any better...
如果這樣能讓你好過點
...when Barry and I got engaged, he was weird too.
我和巴瑞訂婚時他也變了樣
Oh,God. That's what I was afraid of.
瞧,這就是我最擔心的
What's what you were afraid of?
什麼?你擔心什麼?
When Barry was engaged to you, he and l...
巴瑞和你訂婚時,我跟他…
... kind of had a little thing on the side.
…正在偷偷戀愛
-What? -I know,I know.
-什麼? -我知道
When he proposed,people said,"He'll do to you what he did to Rachel."
他向我求婚時,每個人都勸我別接受 他會待你像瑞秋一樣
And now I feel so stupid.
如今我只覺得自己好笨
You are so stupid.
明蒂,你真笨
We are both so stupid.
我們兩人都笨
What do you mean?
什麼意思?
Smell familiar?
是不是熟悉的味?
Oh,I'm so sorry.
抱歉…
Oh,no,me. I am so sorry.
不,是我抱歉…
No,I am sorry. I'm sorry.
不,我對不起,我抱歉
Oh,my.
哦,我的上帝
Four letters,"circle or hoop."
四個字母,圈圈或圓圈
-Ring,damn it,ring. -Thanks.
-快響呀,該死的,快響呀. -謝啦
-You know our phone's not working? -What?
-我們的電話壞了. -什麼?
I called and there was no answer.
我從咖啡店打給你沒有回電
I turned it off.
我關機了
Mother of God,I turned it off.
天啊,我關機了
Just like you told her you did.
和你告訴她的一樣
Just pointing out the irony.
真是諷刺
I went across the street to the doorman.
我和對街門房談過了
I got the peeper's name. Can I use the phone?
他告訴我那偷窺狂的名字,電話能借用嗎?
Can I use your phone?
電話能借用嗎?
The number for a Sidney Marks,please.
請幫我查辛尼馬克斯的電話
"Heating device."
熱裝置?
Radiator.
散熱器
Five letters.
五個字母
"Rdtor."
「Rdtor.」
Yeah,is Sidney there?
是辛尼嗎?
Oh,this is? Sidney's a woman.
辛尼是個女的
So she's a woman,so what?
是女的又怎樣?對,那又怎樣?
Yeah,so what?
對,那又怎樣?
I live across the street,and I know about your telescope.
我住在對街.我注意到你拿著望遠鏡
And I don't appreciate it.
而且我很不喜歡你這樣
Yeah,I can see you right now. Hello?
我現在就看的見你,hello
If I wanna walk around in my underwear,I shouldn't have to feel
如果我要穿著內褲在室內走,我無須感覺…
Thank you.
謝謝
That's not really the point. The point is,that
那不是重點,重點是…
Mostly free-weights, but occasionally
大部份是高速公路,偶爾
Yeah,my neighbor. Yeah,the brunette.
對,我鄰居,對,黑褐色頭髮
She said you looked pretty that day in the green dress.
她說你穿綠色套裝很好看
The green dress? Really?
綠色套裝?真的?
She said you looked like lngrid Bergman.
對,她說你像英格麗褒曼
Did she mention me?
他提到我了嗎?
She wants to know why you tie the towel around your head.
她想知道為什麼你頭上頂塊毛巾
It's a leave-in conditioner,okay?
那是調節器,行不行?
It's a leave-in conditioner.
那是調節器
-You got a second? -Sure,sure.
-你有時間嗎? -當然,當然
Come on...
進來啊…
-...in. -Hello,sweetheart.
hello,親愛的
What you guys doing here?
你們來幹什麼?
We are here to break up with you.
我們是來和你分手的
Both of you?
你們兩個?
We think you're a horrible person, and bad things should happen to you.
基本上我們認為你是個大爛人 你該遭到天打雷劈
I'm sorry. God,I am so sorry.
對不起…我是個白癡
I was weak. I couldn't help myself.
我是個懦夫,我無法自拔
Whatever I did,I only did because I love you so much.
不管我做什麼都是因為太愛你了
Which one of us are you talking to there?
巴瑞,你是指哪一個?
Mindy.
明蒂
Of course,Mindy. It was always Mindy.
當然是指明蒂.我一直深愛著明蒂
When we were having sex in that chair?
即使我們在你椅上做愛?
I swear,whatever I was doing, I was thinking of you.
我發誓,不論我做什麼我都想著你
Please. That second time,you couldn't have picked her out of a lineup.
拜託,第二回合時你連她姓啥都忘了
You did it twice?
你們做了兩次?
The first time didn't really count. You know,it was Barry.
第一次不算,你瞭解巴瑞的
Honey,sweetheart,look. Just give me another chance.
明蒂,我親愛的,再給我一次機會
We'll start over. We'll go back to Aruba.
我們再重新來過,我們再到阿魯巴去
What is it with you and Aruba? Do you have a deal with the airlines?
你和阿魯巴有什麼關係? 你和航空公司有協議嗎?
What do you say?
你怎麼說?
Dr. Farber,we've got an emergency here.
法大夫,緊急狀況
Jason Castalano 's choking on his retainer.
強森被自己的牙套噎到了
Oh,God. I'll be right there,Bernice.
拜託,我馬上去
Look,please don't go anywhere.
請別離開
I'll be right back.
我馬上回來
Okay,and we'll be here, hating you.
我們會在這兒的,在這兒恨你
See how he was sweating when he walked out?
看見他走出去時滿身大汗沒?
If I'm hogging the ball, you jump right in there...
這樣吧,我去抓住他那裡,然後你跳過去
...and take some punches. This feels great.
…狠狠打他幾拳.那感覺一定很爽
I'm pretty sure I'm still gonna marry him.
是嗎?我還是想嫁給她
What are you talking about?
你在說什麼?
Mindy,the guy is the devil.
明蒂,那傢伙是個惡魔
He is Satan in a smock.
是個衣冠禽獸
I know he's not perfect.
我知道他並不完美
But the truth is at the end of the day,I still really wanna be...
老實說我還是想當
... Mrs. Dr. Barry Farber...
巴瑞牙醫的…
... D. D.S.
…太太
Oh,God.
我的天
I hope you can find a way to be happy for me.
希望你能為我高興
And I hope you'll still be my maid of honor.
我希望你還願意當我的伴娘
And I hope Barry doesn't kill you and eat you in Aruba.
我希望巴瑞在阿魯巴不會將你宰了然後吃掉
You okay?
你還好嗎?
Really?
真的嗎?
Since I ran out on Barry at the wedding...
自從我在婚禮上拋下巴瑞
...I've wondered whether I made the right choice.
我一直在想這決定是否正確
And now I know.
如今我已得到答案
I'm so glad.
我真為你高興
Big day.
大日子
I'll give you this: Mr. Peanut is a better dresser.
告訴你花生先生的穿著比較講究
He's got the monocle, he's got the top hat....
他有單片眼鏡,高帽
Did you know he's gay?
你知道他是個男同志嗎?
I just wanna clarify this. Are you outing Mr. Peanut?
我只想知道你判花生先生出局?
Danielle,hi.
丹妮爾
Everybody,this is Danielle. Danielle,everybody.
各位,她叫丹妮爾, 丹妮爾,這是大家
Why are you here?
你為何會出現在這兒?
I've been calling, but I had your number wrong.
我一直打電話給你都一直打錯號碼
When I got the right one, there was no answer.
最後問查號台知道你的號碼 卻沒人接電話
So I thought I'd come down here and make sure you were okay.
我想來看看你是否無恙
I'm okay.
我沒事
Maybe we could get together later?
或許我們改天可以見個面
That sounds good. I'll call you. Or you call me,whatever.
這主意不錯,我再打給你 或是你打給我
You got it.
一言為定
-Bye,everybody. -Bye.
-再見了,各位. -再見
-There you go. -Second date.
-你會和她. -二次約會
I don't know.
我不知道
You don't know?
你不知道?
She seems nice,but her coming all the way here...
她好像很不錯,她大老遠來這兒
...just to see if I was okay? I mean,how needy is that?
只想確定我沒事,有這必要嗎?